bargaincell.com 2011-12-31

# Privacy Notice : BargainCell.com - Bargain Cellular Phone Accessories

At� BargainCell.com, we want you to have the best shopping experience� possible. And while it is necessary for us to collect certain personal� information, we respect and protect your right to privacy. The� following policy is designed to answer any questions and concerns you� may have regarding your privacy and the security of your information.� If you have any additional questions or concerns, please contact us at [CustomerService@BargainCell.com](mailto:CustomerService@BargainCell.com). 

**What Information Do We Collect and How?**

When you order, we need to know your name, e-mail address, mailing� address, credit card number, and expiration date. This allows us to� process your order and to notify you of your order status.

We� may also use the information we collect to occasionally notify you� about important changes to our website, new services, and special� offers we think you'll find valuable. If you would rather not receive� this information, just e-mail us at [CustomerService@BargainCell.com](mailto:CustomerService@BargainCell.com).

 **With Whom Do We Share Your Information?**

BargainCell.com does not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. Period.

 **How We Protect Your Information**

BargainCell.com is committed to protecting the information we receive� from you. Our site encrypts your credit card number and other personal� information using secure socket layer (SSL) technology to provide for� the secure transmission of the information from your PC to our servers.

We have also continuously working with following third party security� vendors to further enchance our web site security and protection.

---|---|---  
  
**Typos and Omissions**

While we try very hard to ensure the accuracy of the information we� provide, we are not responsible for vendor availability, typographical� errors, technical inaccuracies, product pricing errors or omissions.� BargainCell.com has the right to cancel any orders placed for any� product listed at an incorrect price or shown with incorrect� information, whether due to typographical error or otherwise and� whether or not your order was accepted or your credit card charged.� Upon any such cancellation, if your credit card has already been� charged for the purchase, BargainCell.com will promptly issue a full� credit to your account.

 **Changes in Policy**

You� acknowledge that this Privacy Policy is part of the terms of service� and you agree that using this site signifies your assent to� BargainCell.com's Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this Privacy� Policy, please do not use our site. BargainCell.com reserves the right� to change the terms of service, including this Privacy Policy, at any� time. We will post any changes on this page so that you are always� aware of our policy.
